Guide to the Goddard Lieberson Papers
Yale University Music Library
- Correspondence, 1939-1977
  - Lettered correspondence
    - Guinness, Alec (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Guinness, Floria [?] (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Guinzburg, Thomas H. (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Gunther, John & Jane (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Gunther, Nicholas (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Gurson, Sydney (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - H. Keller Troesch & Co. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - H. Koch & Sons, Inc. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - H.M. Baker Associates (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - H.M. Storms Company (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - H.W. Brettell, Ltd. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Haagensen, Cushman (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Hablan, Desi (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Hadassah Bayside Chapter (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Haele, Kay (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Hagen, Uta (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Hagstrom, Karl E. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Hahn, Robert (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Hall, David (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Hall, E.M. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Hall, Edward T. ("Ned") & Mildy (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Hall, Roger G. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Halliday, Richard & Mary Martin (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Ham, Al (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Hamaguchi, Kura (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Hamaguchi, Motoya (Son of Kura) (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Hambleton, T. Edward (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Hambro, Edvard (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Hamburger, Werner (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Hamilton, Russel D. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Hamlisch, Marvin & Lilly (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Hammacher Schlemmer (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Hammerstein II, Oscar (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Hammond, John (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Hannas, Ruth (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Hanson, Howard (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Hanson, Jane (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Hara, Sumio (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Hara-Kiri Magazine (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Harari, Mary (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Hardwicke, Elizabeth (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Harewood, Lord & Countless Patricia (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Harlech, Lord and Lady Pamela (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Harlem Hospital (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Harlem School of Arts (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Harlem Theatre Workshop (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - The Harley School (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Harmarlane Music Ltd. (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Harold Leventhal Management, Inc. (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Harper, Alan A. (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Harper-Atlantic Sales Inc. (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Harper's Bazaar (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Harriman, Averell (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Harrington, Frank L. (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Harris, Barbara (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Harris, Jane (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Harris, Larry (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Harris, Roy (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Harris, Vivian (Mrs. Victor) (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Harrison, Jay (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Harrison, Rex (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Harry N. Abrams, Inc. (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Hart, Moss (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Hartman, Arthur (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Hartog, Howard (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Hartong, H.J.R.G. (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Hartwig, Billie (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Harty, Hamilton (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Hass, J.J. (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Hassard, Donald (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Hatmaker, David J. (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Hatteras Yacht Company (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Haubiel, Charles (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Haverhill's, Inc. (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Hawkins, Hannah, Quail, & Helen (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Hawkins, Mark (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Hayes, J. William (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Hayes, Roland (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Hayward, Leland (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Healy, Don & Viola (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Heckscher, Claude (Mrs. August) (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Hedges, Genevieve (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Heifetz, Jascha (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Heilner, Irwin (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Heiman, Milton (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Heinz II, Henry John ("Jack") & Drue (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Heiskell, Andrew (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Heller, Jackie (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Hellman, Lillian (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Heming, Henry (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Hemingway, Ernest (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Hendl, Walter (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Henrietta Brackman Associates (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Henry A. Evers Company (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Henry M. Snyder & Company (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Henshaw, Jere (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Herman, Jerry (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Herman, Woody (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Herrmann, Bernard (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Hersey, John (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Hertz, David Bendel & Barbara (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Herzog, George (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Higgins, Joseph (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - High Fidelity (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Hildreth, Alice M. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Hill, Jerome (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Hill, Richard S. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Hill, Wolfram (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Hilles, Charles D. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Hilton, Conrad (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Hindemith, Paul (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Hirschfeld, Leonard (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Hirschon, Dorothy (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - His Majesty's Private Secretariat, Bangkok (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Hitchcock, Ethan A. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Hjelm, Carl-Eric (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Hoehn, Kenneth (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Hoffman, Maurice ("Mort") (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Hofmann, Joseph (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Hofstra College (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Holland, Wilfred (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Holliday, Judy (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Hollywood, Daniel (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Holt, Rhinehart and Winston, Inc. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Holtzer, Phyllis S. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Holzman, Jac (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - The Home and School Association of the Southbury Training School, Inc. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Homer, Louise (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - The Hopkins Center (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Hopkins, J. Wallace (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Hopper, Clarence (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Horgan, Paul (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Horizons International, Inc. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Hornblow Jr., Arthur (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Hornblow, Leonora (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Horner, Walter & Co., Inc. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Horowitz, Vladimir & Wanda (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Hostmark, Beth (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Hotel d'Angleterre (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Hotel Continental (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Hotel Hassler (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Hotel & Motel Red Book (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Hotel New Otani (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Hotel Plaza-Athenee (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Hotel Regina Isabella (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - House Plant Corner (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Houseman, John (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Houston Grand Opera (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Howard Hartry, Inc. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Howard, Jack R. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Howard, Norah (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Howell, Miriam (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Huang, Ming Ta (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Hudson River Sloop Restoration, Inc. (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Huff's Gardens (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Humphrey, Hubert H. (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Hunter College (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Huntsman & Sons (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Hurd, Henriette (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Hurd, Peter (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Hurok Concerts Inc. (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Hurok, Sol (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Husby, Mrs. Kellaug (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Huston, John (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Huxley, Aldous & Laura (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Ibuka, Masaru (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Iglehart, Joseph A.W. (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Ilitsch, Daniza (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Illich, Ivan (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Imai, Taho (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Immaculate Heart College (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Imperial Paper Box Company (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Ingersoll, Ralph (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Institute of New Cinema Artists (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - The Inter Dependent (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Interaction Artists, Inc. (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - International Business Machines Corporation (IBM) (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - International Contemporary Music Exchange, Inc. (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - International Federation of Producers of Phonograms and Videograms (IFPI) (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - International Music Council (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - International Telephone and Telegraph Corporation (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - International Videodisc Programming Conference (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Ireland, Charles T. (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Ireland, Mrs. Charles T. [Daphne?] (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Ireland, Margaret (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Irene Hayes Wadley & Smythe (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - IRS (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Isherwood, Christopher (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Ishlon, Deborah (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Island Gardens (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Ives, Charles & Family (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Ives Productions (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Iwama, Mr. & Mrs. Kazuo (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Iwanow, Tatjana (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - J. Miyasaki Productions (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Jablonski, Edward (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Jackson, Nash, Brophy, Barringer & Brooks (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Jacobi, Erwin R. (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Jacobson, Jerry Hart (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Jaffe, Sam (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - James A. Sinclair & Co. Ltd. (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - James, Billy & Judy (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - James, Frances (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - James, Sonny (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Janssen, Herbert (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Japan Publications Trading Co. (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Japan Society (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Jarrets, Mrs. J.M.C. (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Javits, Jacob K. (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Jed, Bruce (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Jeffress, Arthur (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Jelinek, Mrs. Robert (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Jencks, Richard (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Jensen, Mary (Mrs. Clyde Reynolds) (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Jenssen, Per (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Jerome, Henry (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Jewish Teachers Seminary (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Joachim, Louis (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - John Langenbacher Co., Inc. (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Johns Hopkins University (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Johnson, Edward (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Johnson, Geoffrey (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Johnson, J. Rosamond (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Johnson, James Weldon (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Johnson, Luella (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Johnson, Lyndon B. & Lady Bird (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Jonas, Maryla (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Jones, Byron (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Jones, James M. (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Jones, Leslie (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Jones, Merle (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Judd, George E. (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Judson O'Neill Beall & Steinway Inc. (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Jurgens, Curt (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Kagan, Alfred (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Kagawa, Lawrence T. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Kahn, Albert E. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Kahn, Kermit (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Kalenin, George (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Kalinski, Felix (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Kalischer, Peter (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Kalman, Emmerich (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Kanata Records Limited (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Kane, Harriet T. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Kaneko, Hizuru ("Shoo") (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Kanin, Garson (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Kantor, Joseph (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Kanzaki, Johji (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Kapelner, Alan (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Kaplan, Livingston, Goodwin & Berkowitz (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Kapp, Paul (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Kapralik, David (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Karlin, Fred (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Karp, Harvey (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Kass, Ron (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Katz, Jetti (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Katz, Therese R. (Mrs. Abram J.) (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Kavan, Stanley J. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Kawai Musical Instruments (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Kaye, Danny & Sylvia (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Kaye, Sydney (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Kazenoff, Harry (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Keating, Cornelius ("Neil") (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Keats, Sheila (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Keiser, Sylvia (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Kellerman, Mrs. J.A. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Kelly, Gene (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Kemeny, Jean A. (Mrs. John G.) (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Kemp, Lou (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Kennedy, Edward M. (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Kennedy, Ethel (Mrs. Robert F.) (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Kennedy, Jacqueline Onassis (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Kennedy, John F. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Kennedy, Joseph P. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Kennedy, Robert F. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Kennedy, Rose (Mrs. Joseph P.) (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Kennedy, Ted (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Keoseian, Richard S. (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Kern, Jerome & Eva (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Kerr, Walter (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Khempco Supply (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Kiepura, Jan (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Kiesler, Frederick J. (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Kimiko, Jo (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Kindler, Arthur (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - King, Alexander & Margie (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - King, Bruce (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Kings Flowers Inc. (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Kinnear, William (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Kinney, James R. (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Kinntorph, Boo (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Kipness, Joseph (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Kirkpatrick, John (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Kirstein, Lincoln (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Kleban, Ed (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Klein, Alexander (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Klein Sleep Products (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Klemmer, Raymond J. (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Klemperer, Otto (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Klingbeil Company (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Klopfer, Mr. & Mrs. Donald (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - KMYR (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Knickerbocker Hospital (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Knoll International (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Knopf, Alfred & Helen (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Kobley & Stern Inc. (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Koike, Y. (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Kollek, Teddy (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Kolodin, Irving (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Koppelman, Charles (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Kornheiser, Audrey & Sidney (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Korvette's (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Kosakima, Phyllis (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Koshetz, Marina (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Kosinsky, Jerzy & Kim (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Koss, Leopold (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Kostelanetz, Andre (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Kostelanetz, Andre (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Kostelanetz, Andre (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Koussevitzky, Serge (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Kraft, Robert (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Kraft, Ethel Lieberson (Sister) (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Krasner, Louis (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Krasnow, Hermann (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Kraus, Robert G. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Krayer, James C. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Krementz, Jill (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Kresh, Paul (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Kreuger, Miles (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Kristofferson, Kris (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Kroo, Alexander (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Kurebayashi, Kozue (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Kurebayashi, Shigeo (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Kurland, John (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Kurnitz, Harry (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Kurtz, Mr. & Mrs. Efrem (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Kuzumi, Tomi (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Kyle, Betty & Steve (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Laborde, Monique (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Labrie, Gene (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - La Farge, Oliver (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Lake, Jim (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Lake Shore Central Schools (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Lambton, Lady Belinda ("Bindy") (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Lamereux, William W. (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Land, Norman (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Landers, Hal (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Lang, Bernard (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Langenberg, Mrs. J.W.A. (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Langendorff, Mrs. F.J. (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Language World (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Laning, Caleb B. (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Lansbury, Angela (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Lansbury, Edgar (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Lantz, Robert (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Larcada, Richard K. (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Larsen, Patricia & Jorgen (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - La Salle Sr. High School (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Lateiner, Jacob (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Lauer, Elizabeth (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Laurents, Arthur (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Lauria, Mary (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - LaVere, Stephen C. (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Lawford, Peter (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Laurence, Marjorie (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Lawrence, Sheldon (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Lawrence, Vera Brodsky (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Lawson, Wendall (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Layton, Joe (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Lazar, Irving Paul (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Lazard Freres & Co. (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Leahy, James (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Leal, Rogerio (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Leavitt, Max (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Lebensohn, Zigmund (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Leber-Krebs Inc. (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - LeClerq, Tanaquil (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Lee, Edmund J. (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Lee, Peggy (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Lees, Mr. (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Lefcourt, Jesse L. (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Legman, Gershon (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Lehman, Lotte (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Lehrer, Tom (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Leigh, Vivian (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Leighton, Margaret (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Leimbacher, Ed (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Leinsdorf, Erich & Anne (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Leiser, Jacques (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Lemmon, Jack (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Lensrud, John (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Lent, David (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Lenya, Lotte (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Leo, William (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Leonard, Bill (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Leonard, Margery (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Lerman, Leo (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Lerner, Alan Jay (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Lerolle-Chausson, Mrs. P. (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Lesko, John (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Leslie, Cole (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Leslie, Don (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Leslie, Seymour (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Levant, Lorna (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Levant, Oscar & June (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Leventon, Alexander (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Levi, Pilade (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Levin, Herman (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Levine, Maurice (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Levinson, Peter (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Levitan, Alice (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Levitt, Mrs. Mortimer (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Levy, Billie (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Levy, Len (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Levy, Leon (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Levy, Leonard S. (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Lew, Isaih (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Lewando, Olga & Ralph (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Lewis, Edward (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - L.F. Rothschild & Co. (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Lhevinne, Rosina (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Liberman, Anna (Mrs. Myron S.) (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Liberman, Alexander (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Library of Congress (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Library & Museum of the Performing Arts (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Library of Presidential Papers (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Lieberman, Rolf (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Lieberson, Abraham & Rachel (Parents) (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Lieberson, Dennis Neil (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Lieberson, Gershon Lee (Brother) (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Lieberson, Jonathan (Son) (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Lieberson, Jonathan (Son) (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Lieberson, Maurice ("Moish" - Brother) (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Lieberson, Peter (Son) (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Liebling, Jean (Mrs. A.J.) (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Lieoentjiep, Paul (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Lieurance, Thurlow (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Lifkei, Ervin (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Lincoln College (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Lincoln Herald (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Lindsay, Howard (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Lindsay, Mary (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Lindstrom, Jenny (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Lindt, Lotte (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Lipton, Shelley (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Lissim, Simon (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Little, Brown & Company (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - The Little Orchestra of London (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - The Lively Arts (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Livingston, Alan (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Livingston Communications, Inc. (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Livingston, Robert (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Livingston School (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Lloyd, Norman (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Lloyd, Peggy (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Lockwood, Joseph (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Loesser, Frank (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Loesser, Jo Sullivan (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Loetz, E. Jack (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Loewe, Frederick (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Logan, Joshua & Nedda (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Logan, Susan (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Logan, Tom (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Loggins, Ken & Jim Messina (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Loken, Robert (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Long, Robert (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Long, Russell B. (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Lorber, Alfred B. (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Loren, Pamela (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Lorenz, John J. ("Jack") (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Loreto, Michael Joseph & Mabel (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Los Angeles Philharmonic Orchestra (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Losey, Joseph (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Lost Cause Press (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Lotos Club (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Loveman, Sam (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Lovett, Robert A. (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Lowenthal, Freedman, Landau, Fischer & Todres (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Lowry, W. McNeil (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Luening, Otto (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Lundvall, Bruce (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Lunt, Alfred & Lynn Fontaine (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Lurie, H. Lee (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Lurie, Mendel (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Lynd, Terence (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Lyons, Douglas (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Lyons, Sylvia & Leonard (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Macauley, Cathy (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - MacCowatt (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - MacDonald, Betty (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - MacDonald Forbes Flower Shop (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - MacDowell Colony (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Macero, Teo (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Machat, Martin (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - MacIntosh, David (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Mackenzie, Wendy (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - MacPherson, Gardens (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Madrigal Publications (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Magaloff, Nikita & Irene (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - The Magic Flute Record Shop (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Magnat, Th. Dominique (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Magro, Frank (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Maguire, Charles M. (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Mahler-Werfel, Alma (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Maigret, Mr. & Mrs. Jean-Louis (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Mainbocher (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Mallett, Donald (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Mallory, Shawn (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Maloy, Barbara (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Malraux, Madeleine (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Mana Maeda Design (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Management Communications Inc. (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Borough of Manhattan, Office of the President (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Manhattan Cable (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Manhattan Country School (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Manhattan Theatre Club (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Manhattanville Community Centers Inc. (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Manion, John J. (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Mankiewicz, Joseph L. (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Mann, Dave (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Mann, Erika (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Mann, Thomas (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Mannes College of Music (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Mannes, Leopold (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Manuel, Michael (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Marchi, John J. (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Marek, George (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Margulis, Walter P. (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Marin, Georges (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Marín, Inés M. de Muñoz (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Mark Cross Pens (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Marlboro Music (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Marlowe, Sylvia (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Marquis Who's Who Inc. (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Marsh Hospital for Animals (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Marshall, Bratter, Greene, Allison & Tucker (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Marti, Gloria (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Martin, Elliot (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Martin Goodman Productions, Inc. (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Martino, Joe (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Marx, Groucho (Box 14, Folder 7)